between is that the
term founder friendly got
perverse to a where
if a VC doesn't
act like the exceptional
doesn't play themselves with
less leverage and gives
founders all the leverage
then they're deemed like
a bad VC Got
it You know and
so there was this
idea that all VCs
should act like every
founder is just like
a Facebook Like Mark
Zuckerberg got away with
full control of a
very large public company
through the PrefShare stuff
you and many founders
which I shall not
name even from Southeast
Asia managed to get
that too for very
significant companies So they
have like complete control
over like a behemoth
of a and well
deserved because they had
the But at the
same time is that
there's this idea that
if you're in like
a company that may
not become a Facebook
or may not become
a for example that
you deserve the same
treatment Yeah you don't
get that Yeah you
you want the same
treatment You feel deserve
the same treatment because
there's this moral view
you know that like
VC should just like
bend over and serve
and just you know
and in this way